The next information coming out is the
share price here is ₹15 and the name of this company
is ICI LBAR, their results have come out,
friends, their quarterly results came
in September, etc. We will give you
some short information about this, stay tuned,
we will tell you, you will understand a little,
okay, we will talk about it here, they have
released approximately in the quarter of 2025,
their profit has increased by 12%
here, it has become ₹56516 crore,
friends, if
we talk about this year after the previous year, then what was there in the same period was
₹5255 crore, friends, so that
means ₹255 crore remained the same in September 2024,
this time their profit in September 2025 was
₹56516 crore, there has been an increase of around 12%,
here their total income has been, if we
talk about net profit, then there has been a
value increase of 8% and what has happened is
₹6939 crore, okay  It has increased from Rs. 100 crore to
₹8195 crore, which means
if we talk about last September 2020, the profit was ₹6949
crore.  This time
their profit has been ₹8195 crores, approximately
₹8200 crores,
whatever the above figure is.  If we talk about profit, it has been
₹172
crores.
If we talk about the same thing in the previous year, it was ₹9190 crores.
So this is also very good.  It
is very big.  On 23rd October, they are going to
give a dividend of 35% and 65%
and
you are going to
get the dividend here as per the share of ₹6.  No matter how many shares you have,
you will get dividend here at the
rate of ₹6.5 per share.  You
can subscribe to my channel for such financial news.  I will keep bringing you videos like this for updates.
Friends, if you have not subscribed to the channel,
please do subscribe.  See you
in the next video.  Jai Hind.